http://drumsonsale.com/privacy-policy

Drums on SALE
0 items in cart.
Checkout
You have no items in your shopping cart.
X
No.
Privacy Policy
Drums on SALE is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. To demonstrate this commitment, Drums on SALE has created this privacy policy governing the use of information collected through this web site. By accessing and viewing this you agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In order to access certain portions of the web site you will be required to register by providing certain limited information regarding you and/or the company you represent.
Account Registration
In order to use many features of the web site you will be asked to complete an account registration form. During registration, you are required to provide contact information. Drums on SALE may use this contact information as a means of confirmation of your identity. We use this information to provide you with quality services as well as with offers that we think are relevant to you our customer. Please see the Information Sharing and Disclosure section below. Using your contact information, Drums on SALE may also send you e-mail messages under the following circumstances, among others:
To respond to an inquiry or request for information
To thank you for contacting Drums on SALE
To welcome you to Drums on SALE and to its products and services
To explain new product offerings and features of our services
To notify you of special promotions
To communicate with you regarding customer service related issues.
In order to maintain accurate records concerning communications that Drums on SALE may have received from or sent to you, Drums on SALE may also indefinitely store any information that you provide to Drums on SALE through the web site.
Do we use "cookies"?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Once you register on this site, you are providing Drums on SALE with personally identifiable information. Drums on SALE will not share, disclose, or sell this information to any third party – it is solely for our own internal use.
Special Offers
We do not provide copies of our email subscriber database information to third parties. As a Registered User and based on the preferences you share at registration, you will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals and newsletters. Out of respect for your privacy we present the option to not receive these types of communications.
Users Outside of the United States
While we make every effort to honor the laws and wishes of all users, this Web Site is available for users located exclusively in the United States of America and therefore may not recognize foreign laws.
Security Precautions
Drums on SALE takes precautions to protect data and information under its control from misuse, loss or alteration. Drums on SALE security measures include industry-standard technology and equipment to help protect your information, and Drums on SALE maintains security measures to allow only the appropriate personnel access to your information. Unfortunately, no system can ensure complete security, and Drums on SALE disclaims any liability resulting from use of this web site. If you have any questions about the security at our web sites, please send contact us.
Exceptions
Other than as set forth above, Drums on SALE will not otherwise use or disclose any of your personal information except to the extent reasonably necessary to: (i) process your information and to correct technical problems and malfunctions in the Website or the computer systems supporting the Website; (ii) protect the security and integrity of the Website; (iii) protect the rights and property of Drums on SALE and others; (iv) take precautions against liability; (v) respond to claims that your information violates the rights and interests of third-parties; (vi) respond to judicial or administrative process or otherwise comply with applicable law; and (vii) to assist law enforcement agencies in connection with investigations or matters related to public safety.
Updating Personal Information
You may update or correct information you previously provided to Drums on SALE by accessing your user account on our web site.
Questions or Comments Regarding the Privacy Policy
For additional questions, or to be taken off our marketing lists, please send contact us.
